# **Aatish Kumar Moharana**

Cuttack, Odisha | 6371061240 aatishkumarmoharana@gmail.com

### **Summary**

2nd year Computer Science Engineer at Odisha University Of Technology And Research, Bhubaneswar having the skills of Hardwork, to Design Website. I know the fundamentals of HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT PHP MYSQL NODEJS. I have experience of only 1 WebDevelopment Hackathon.

## **Experience**

#### MyCaptain

### Campus Ambassador | 08/2021 - 09/2021

I was the campus ambassador of MyCaptain. I was given the role to Build trust among the students on MyCaptain.

#### Spectrum

# Web Developer Intern | 06/2021 - 07/2021

I learnt Html CSS Javascript Php MySql During that period of 30days

The Website I made https://keen-rosalind-6ebd32.netlify.app/

### Zairza Club Cet Bhubaneswar

### Web Development Intern | 06/2021 - 07/2021

Basically Zairza Club Of Our College Started Skill++ program for 30 days . I learnt HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT NODEJS during that time

Website I made during task 2 https://aatish1111.github.io/Zairza Task 2/

### Developer Days(Devfolio)

#### 09/2021 - 10/2021

It was basically a hackathon in which My Teamate and I participated at that time I was in 22 in leaderboard. We created Edify(not hosted it) <a href="https://github.com/Saikiran-Mohanty/Edify.git">https://github.com/Saikiran-Mohanty/Edify.git</a> as the final project during that time.

My portfolio Website that I made during that period https://aatish1111.github.io/React-portfolio/

#### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, C++, SQL, Mysql, Python

#### **Education**

# DAV PUBLIC SCHOOL CDA SEC-6 CUTTACK | Cuttack, Odisha Class 10th and Class 12th

In Class 10th I secured 93.8%. In Class 12th I secured 94.2%

# Languages

English, Hindi